http://www.restaurantnews.com/privacy-policy/

Your Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie
Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.
To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.
Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, RestaurantNews.com has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.
Collection of Personal Information
When visiting RestaurantNews.com, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Links to third party Websites
We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.
Changes to this Privacy Statement
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.
If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of RestaurantNews.com then you may contact us at troy@restaurantnews.com
Last updated Sat, 31 Jul 2010 06:31
Restaurant Franchise Opportunities Recent PostsFocus Brands Announces Departure of Industry VeteranTropical Smoothie Cafe Announces +26.3% Same Store Sales in NovemberFazoli’s Selects Five Out of 5,000 Employees to be Named to All-American TeamUS Foods Introduces New COVID-19 Resources to Help Restaurant Operators Address Ongoing Winter ChallengesNew Straw Hat Pizza NOW OPEN in Rocklin, CASay ‘Good Riddance’ to 2020 with Old Chicago Pizza & Taproom’s Exclusive Limited-Edition IPADickey’s Barbecue Pit Helps Bring the Magic of Christmas to More Children this YearCurry Up Now Inks Second Franchise Deal in Texas Within the Past MonthCrave Hot Dogs and BBQ to Open in Canton, MichiganSlice Factory Hosts Grand Opening Event in BurbankDQ Grill & Chill Restaurant Coming to ArdmoreMy Friend’s Place Deli Announces New Distribution Agreement with Gordon Food ServiceTeriyaki Madness to Celebrate Opening in Overland Park on December 10Corner Bakery Launches Easy, Safe and Convenient Curbside Pickup ProgramSan Pedro Fish Market Unveils 12 Days of Shrimp Dec 9 – 20Jeremiah’s Italian Ice Continues Expansion in Volusia CountyLet’s Do Trivia! Goes 100% Contact-FreeDickey’s Barbecue Pit Executes Key Franchise Deal to Expand Into JapanChicken Salad Chick Continues Rapid Expansion in Louisiana With New Restaurant Opening in Bossier CityQuaker Steak & Lube Ready to Serve SalemFront Burner’s New Slider Concept – Son of a Butcher – Makes Stand-Alone Debut in Lower GreenvilleEl Pollo Loco Celebrates 40th Anniversary with Throwback to Original LogoOur Kind of Town: Smoothie King Targets Chicago for Continued ExpansionNational Franchise Sales Advisor Ritchie Labate Promoted to Managing DirectorBlaze Fast-Fire’d Pizza Announces Grand Opening of New Texas LocationMilkshake Concepts Names Champion PR Agency of RecordForget the Stress of Cooking this Holiday Season with TooJay’s DeliIsland Fin Poké Announces 20 New Restaurants Coming to West FloridaFazoli’s Sets Brand Records with Six Months of Historical Sales and TrafficCurry Up Now Launches New Low Proof Cocktails at All Bay Area LocationsNYC’s The Hummus & Pita Co. to Debut in Huntsville, AlabamaTeriyaki Madness Arrives in Downtown Los Angeles on December 10Teriyaki Madness Pushes Loyalty Program Into OverdriveMOOYAH Burgers, Fries & Shakes Continues Supporting Communities with New Digital Fundraising ProgramFollow Us
